https://www.nelsontreehouse.com/privacy-policy

Shop
Design + Build/OverviewFAQDesign + Build StepsConsultGallery
Privacy Policy for nelsontreehouse.com
Design + Build/OverviewFAQDesign + Build StepsConsultGallery
Shop/
PRIVACY POLICYTransparency and your privacy are important to us. Please review our Privacy Policy, below.You can review our Terms of Use, here.Last updated 7.31.2018SQUARESPACEOur website is hosted by Squarespace. Your data is stored through Squarespace’s databases, on a secure server behind a firewall. We recommend that you read Squarespace’s policies so you can understand the manner in which your user information may be handled by Squarespace:   Squarespace Terms of Service https://www.squarespace.com/terms-of-service/Squarespace Privacy Policy: https://www.squarespace.com/privacy/Squarespace Acceptable Use Policy: https://www.squarespace.com/acceptable-use-policySquarespace Cookie Policy: https://www.squarespace.com/cookie-policy/DEVICE INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE ITWhen you visit our site, we collect your device information in order to enhance your overall experience on our site. You can browse our site without submitting any personally identifiable information, but we do collect some anonymous information when you access our site.We collect device information using the following technologies:“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.“Log files” track actions occurring on the site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the site.Location information: Your devices (depending on your settings) may transmit location information to our site. We use this information to customize, improve, and protect our site.Analytics information: Squarespace uses analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for our site. These tools collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including the web pages you visit, your browser add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving our site. We may collect and use this analytics information together with any additional personal information you provide and stitch together session data from user visits to build a broader profile of our individual users so that we can serve you better.When you visit a page on our site, we may receive information about your visit such as:DateTimeIP addressReferrerBrowser versionOperating systemDemographic and profile dataThis information gives us insight into, among other things:Our visitors’ geographic location by IP addressHow visitors in specific locations find our siteWe also monitor traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and improve the design and layout of the site.COOKIES: Cookies are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.Squarespace and our other service provides may use cookies (both session cookies and persistent cookie) to analyze trends, administer our site, track your movements around our site, better understand how you interact with our site, determine interest in particular content and monitor aggregate usage by visitors and online traffic routing. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis. You may be able to instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the online services you visit. You may also remove persistent cookies by following your web browser’s help file directions. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of our site or all functionality of our site.Squarespace and our other service providers may also use “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “clear GIFs,” or similar means in connection with our site to, among other things, track the actions of users, to determine the success of marketing campaigns and to compile aggregate statistics about site usage and response rates.Squarespace uses these technologies to do things such as remember your preferences, keep you safe and improve and promote their services. You can read more about how Squarespace uses these technologies in their Cookie Policy.PERSONAL INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOUOPTING INTO MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS: When you visit our site, you may be invited to provide personal information to join our emailing list for marketing communications. We will either ask you directly for your expressed consent to join our emailing list, or provide you with an opportunity to say no. You can choose to opt into our emailing list marketing communications by: completing the subscription form(s) on the site. We will use the personal information (including your name, email address, and device information) you provide on these forms to be in touch with you and to provide updates and marketing communications via email. You can change your mind at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email you receive from us, or by contacting us at blog@nelsontreehouseandsupply.com. We will treat your information with respect. We use MailChimp as our marketing automation platform. By clicking to submit any of these marketing subscription forms, you acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their Privacy Policy and Terms.By entering your information and clicking to receive our marketing communcations, you agree that we may process your personal information in accordance with these terms.From this point forward, when we talk about “user information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about device information and personal information.AGE OF CONSENTThis site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18. By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.COPYRIGHT NOTICEAll text, images, graphics, sounds, and software code ("Content") on this site are copyrighted property of Nelson Treehouse and Supply, its contributors, and its programmers unless otherwise noted. They may only be used for the personal education of site visitors. They may not be placed in the public domain. You may not reproduce, redistribute, publish, or otherwise use by electronic or any other means any of the Content without our prior written consent.TRADEMARKSNelson Treehouse and Supply and other marks indicated on our site are service marks of Nelson Treehouse and Supply. They may not be used or displayed without the prior written consent of Nelson Treehouse and Supply. All other trademarks, product names, and company names and logos appearing on the site are the property of their respective owners.INFORMATION SHARED WITH THIRD PARTIESHOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION: We use the user information you provide us when opting into our marketing communications to communicate with you and provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. We also use your user information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).We may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals we trust and partner with to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and email, conducting sweepstakes and other promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These agents have access to user  information needed to perform their functions. Other than our outside agents and certain suppliers and vendors, we keep all of your user information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so.Nelson Treehouse and Supply may also release user information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Nelson Treehouse and Supply, our affiliated businesses, users, or others. We may disclose your user information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service. We may also share your user information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your user information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your user information will be handled by these providers.Certain items from Be in a Tree, our online treehouse supply store, may be featured on the Nelson Treehouse site. If you choose to place an order for any of these items featured on the Nelson Treehouse site, you will be directed to Be in a Tree’s external website which is separate and distinct from the Nelson Treehouse website. We recommend that you read Be in a Tree’s policies so you can understand the manner in which your user information may be handled by Be in a Tree.Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Use.SECURITYTo protect your user information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.We strive to protect your user information; however, Nelson Treehouse and Supply cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.LINKSWhen you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements. Certain content, products and services available via our site may include materials from third-parties.Third-party links on this site may direct you to third-party websites that are not affiliated with us. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating the content or accuracy and we do not warrant and will not have any liability or responsibility for any third-party materials or websites, or for any other materials, products, or services of third-parties.We are not liable for any harm or damages related to the purchase or use of goods, services, resources, content, or any other transactions made in connection with any third-party websites. Please review carefully the third-party's policies and practices and make sure you understand them before you engage in any transaction. Complaints, claims, concerns, or questions regarding third-party products should be directed to the third-party. USER COMMENTS, FEEDBACK AND OTHER SUBMISSIONSIf, at our request, you send certain specific submissions (for example contest entries) or without a request from us you send creative ideas, suggestions, proposals, plans, or other materials, whether online, by email, by postal mail, or otherwise (collectively, 'comments'), you agree that we may, at any time, without restriction, edit, copy, publish, distribute, translate and otherwise use in any medium any comments that you forward to us. We are and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any comments in confidence; (2) to pay compensation for any comments; or (3) to respond to any comments. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor, edit or remove content that we determine in our sole discretion are unlawful, offensive, threatening, libelous, defamatory, pornographic, obscene or otherwise objectionable or violates any party’s intellectual property or our Terms of Use.You agree that your comments will not violate any right of any third-party, including copyright, trademark, privacy, personality or other personal or proprietary right. You further agree that your comments will not contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive or obscene material, or contain any computer virus or other malware that could in any way affect the operation of this site or any related website. You may not use a false e-mail address, pretend to be someone other than yourself, or otherwise mislead us or third-parties as to the origin of any comments. You are solely responsible for any comments you make and their accuracy. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for any comments posted by you or any third-party.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access user information we hold about you and to ask that your user information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information at the bottom of this page.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your user information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you visit this Site, and if you choose to provide personal information to sign up for our marketing communications, we will maintain your user information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMSBy visiting the Nelson Treehouse site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to the collection and use of this information by Nelson Treehouse and Supply. We will always fully disclose our privacy policies, and we will promptly post any changes to our policy on this page.You agree that Nelson Treehouse and Supply may retain and use your device information and personal information (collectively, "user information") as described in this policy until you inform us that you do not agree with this Privacy Policy and agree that you will not use the Nelson Treehouse website for a reasonable period of time thereafter.By using this site after we post any changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to accept those changes. If you choose to visit the Nelson Treehouse website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy.QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you have any questions about our Privacy Policy and/or Terms of Use, the practices of this Site, or your interactions with this website, you may contact: Website Privacy Compliance Officer at blog@nelsontreehouseandsupply.com or by mail at: Nelson Treehouse and Supply, Re: Website Privacy Compliance Officer, PO Box 1135 Fall City Washington US 98024
Design + Build/OverviewFAQDesign + Build StepsConsultGallery
Stay/
Blog/
TV Show/
Our Story/
Our Crew/
Press/
Shop/
Nelson Treehouse
Home of all things Nelson Treehouse: find information here on Pete Nelson and the Treehouse Masters, building treehouses with Nelson Treehouse and Supply, treehouse hardware, and TreeHouse Point.
NELSON FAMILY
READ OUR STORY
CONNECT WITH US
TO THE BLOG
SHOP
VIDEOS
Contact Us
We use cookies to improve your experience on our website. By interacting with our site, you acknowledge and agree to this. Learn More
THIS WEEK AT NELSON TREEHOUSE AND SUPPLY
THIS WEEK AT TREEHOUSE POINT
Email Address
Sign Up
Nelson Treehouse will use the information you provide on this form to be in touch with you and to provide updates and marketing via email. You can change your mind at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email you receive from us, or by contacting us at info@nelsontreehouseandsupply.com. We will treat your information with respect.For more information about our privacy practices please email info@nelsontreehouseandsupply.com or visit our privacy policy webpage. By clicking above, you agree that we may process your information in accordance with these terms.We use MailChimp as our marketing automation platform. By clicking above to submit this form, you acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their Privacy Policy and Terms.
Thank you!
VISIT TREEHOUSE POINT
SHOP
BUILD A TREEHOUSE
CONTACT US | BLOG ARCHIVES | TERMS OF USE | PRIVACY POLICY | CAREERS
We use cookies to improve your experience on our website. By interacting with our site, you acknowledge and agree to this. Learn MoreCopyright © 2012-2019 Nelson Treehouse and Supply — All rights reserved PO BOX 1135, FALL CITY, WA 98024Oregon CCB # 210388
Posted by Nelson Treehouse and Supply
